limpbizkit.org 2000-08-15

# Privacy Statement of The JoeDavison.com Network

##  Privacy Statement for The JoeDavison.com Network 

**The JoeDavison.com Network** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ The JoeDavison.com Network ](http://www.joedavison.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. 

####  Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration forms may require users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Surveys 

Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (like email address), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the surveys is used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Contests 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the contests is used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **The JoeDavison.com Network** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Our lists are managed by PostMasterDirect/Netcreations, the leaders in opt-in email marketing, whose systems provide a great deal of security with regards to your personal information. 

####  Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us. 

  1. To opt-out of any of our email lists, please visit PosMasterDirect, located at [http://www.postmasterdirect.com](http://www.postmasterdirect.com/).

For all other information regarding opt-out, please contact [support@joedavison.com](mailto:support@joedavison.com). 

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. To submit any questions or desired modifications, please contact [. support@joedavison.com ](mailto:support@joedavison.com)

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
